{
    "levels": [
        {
            "type": "addition",
            "difficulties": [
                {
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 1,
                            "question": "1 + 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 6,
                            "choices": [
                                6,
                                5,
                                7
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 2,
                            "question": "10 + 4",
                            "correctAnswer": 14,
                            "choices": [
                                14,
                                15,
                                13
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 3,
                            "question": "9 + 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 15,
                            "choices": [
                                15,
                                14,
                                16
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 4,
                            "question": "2 + 8",
                            "correctAnswer": 10,
                            "choices": [
                                10,
                                9,
                                11
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 5,
                            "question": "6 + 1",
                            "correctAnswer": 7,
                            "choices": [
                                8,
                                7,
                                6
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 6,
                            "question": "1 + 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 4,
                            "choices": [
                                4,
                                3,
                                5
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 7,
                            "question": "1 + 9",
                            "correctAnswer": 10,
                            "choices": [
                                11,
                                9,
                                10
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 8,
                            "question": "6 + 2",
                            "correctAnswer": 8,
                            "choices": [
                                7,
                                9,
                                8
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 9,
                            "question": "1 + 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 7,
                            "choices": [
                                7,
                                8,
                                6
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 10,
                            "question": "5 + 1",
                            "correctAnswer": 6,
                            "choices": [
                                7,
                                6,
                                5
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 11,
                            "question": "10 + 7",
                            "correctAnswer": 17,
                            "choices": [
                                18,
                                17,
                                16
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 12,
                            "question": "3 + 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 9,
                            "choices": [
                                10,
                                9,
                                8
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 13,
                            "question": "3 + 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 9,
                            "choices": [
                                9,
                                10,
                                8
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 14,
                            "question": "6 + 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 9,
                            "choices": [
                                8,
                                10,
                                9
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 15,
                            "question": "3 + 1",
                            "correctAnswer": 4,
                            "choices": [
                                5,
                                3,
                                4
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 16,
                            "question": "5 + 8",
                            "correctAnswer": 13,
                            "choices": [
                                12,
                                13,
                                14
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 17,
                            "question": "4 + 9",
                            "correctAnswer": 13,
                            "choices": [
                                13,
                                14,
                                12
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 18,
                            "question": "3 + 10",
                            "correctAnswer": 13,
                            "choices": [
                                12,
                                13,
                                14
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 19,
                            "question": "10 + 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 16,
                            "choices": [
                                16,
                                15,
                                17
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 20,
                            "question": "1 + 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 7,
                            "choices": [
                                6,
                                8,
                                7
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 21,
                            "question": "41 + 70",
                            "correctAnswer": 111,
                            "choices": [
                                111,
                                112,
                                110
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 22,
                            "question": "67 + 41",
                            "correctAnswer": 108,
                            "choices": [
                                107,
                                109,
                                108
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 23,
                            "question": "40 + 94",
                            "correctAnswer": 134,
                            "choices": [
                                134,
                                135,
                                133
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 24,
                            "question": "28 + 87",
                            "correctAnswer": 115,
                            "choices": [
                                115,
                                114,
                                116
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 25,
                            "question": "67 + 40",
                            "correctAnswer": 107,
                            "choices": [
                                107,
                                108,
                                106
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 26,
                            "question": "78 + 35",
                            "correctAnswer": 113,
                            "choices": [
                                114,
                                112,
                                113
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 27,
                            "question": "69 + 100",
                            "correctAnswer": 169,
                            "choices": [
                                169,
                                170,
                                168
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 28,
                            "question": "28 + 96",
                            "correctAnswer": 124,
                            "choices": [
                                123,
                                125,
                                124
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 29,
                            "question": "76 + 89",
                            "correctAnswer": 165,
                            "choices": [
                                164,
                                165,
                                166
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 30,
                            "question": "23 + 27",
                            "correctAnswer": 50,
                            "choices": [
                                50,
                                49,
                                51
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 31,
                            "question": "54 + 39",
                            "correctAnswer": 93,
                            "choices": [
                                93,
                                94,
                                92
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 32,
                            "question": "95 + 38",
                            "correctAnswer": 133,
                            "choices": [
                                132,
                                133,
                                134
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 33,
                            "question": "19 + 90",
                            "correctAnswer": 109,
                            "choices": [
                                109,
                                110,
                                108
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 34,
                            "question": "43 + 49",
                            "correctAnswer": 92,
                            "choices": [
                                91,
                                93,
                                92
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 35,
                            "question": "11 + 30",
                            "correctAnswer": 41,
                            "choices": [
                                42,
                                41,
                                40
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 36,
                            "question": "14 + 74",
                            "correctAnswer": 88,
                            "choices": [
                                89,
                                88,
                                87
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 37,
                            "question": "49 + 87",
                            "correctAnswer": 136,
                            "choices": [
                                136,
                                135,
                                137
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 38,
                            "question": "13 + 67",
                            "correctAnswer": 80,
                            "choices": [
                                81,
                                80,
                                79
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 39,
                            "question": "74 + 69",
                            "correctAnswer": 143,
                            "choices": [
                                142,
                                143,
                                144
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 40,
                            "question": "68 + 21",
                            "correctAnswer": 89,
                            "choices": [
                                88,
                                90,
                                89
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 41,
                            "question": "4565 + 4141",
                            "correctAnswer": 8706,
                            "choices": [
                                8707,
                                8705,
                                8706
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 42,
                            "question": "3058 + 1096",
                            "correctAnswer": 4154,
                            "choices": [
                                4155,
                                4153,
                                4154
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 43,
                            "question": "2091 + 1239",
                            "correctAnswer": 3330,
                            "choices": [
                                3331,
                                3329,
                                3330
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 44,
                            "question": "1145 + 3434",
                            "correctAnswer": 4579,
                            "choices": [
                                4579,
                                4580,
                                4578
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 45,
                            "question": "1808 + 2046",
                            "correctAnswer": 3854,
                            "choices": [
                                3853,
                                3854,
                                3855
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 46,
                            "question": "1639 + 2537",
                            "correctAnswer": 4176,
                            "choices": [
                                4176,
                                4175,
                                4177
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 47,
                            "question": "3879 + 2363",
                            "correctAnswer": 6242,
                            "choices": [
                                6243,
                                6241,
                                6242
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 48,
                            "question": "2389 + 4392",
                            "correctAnswer": 6781,
                            "choices": [
                                6781,
                                6780,
                                6782
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 49,
                            "question": "4431 + 2697",
                            "correctAnswer": 7128,
                            "choices": [
                                7129,
                                7127,
                                7128
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 50,
                            "question": "4170 + 2343",
                            "correctAnswer": 6513,
                            "choices": [
                                6512,
                                6514,
                                6513
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 51,
                            "question": "2604 + 4295",
                            "correctAnswer": 6899,
                            "choices": [
                                6898,
                                6900,
                                6899
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 52,
                            "question": "4417 + 2238",
                            "correctAnswer": 6655,
                            "choices": [
                                6655,
                                6656,
                                6654
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 53,
                            "question": "4073 + 3834",
                            "correctAnswer": 7907,
                            "choices": [
                                7908,
                                7907,
                                7906
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 54,
                            "question": "2794 + 3569",
                            "correctAnswer": 6363,
                            "choices": [
                                6364,
                                6363,
                                6362
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 55,
                            "question": "3449 + 3999",
                            "correctAnswer": 7448,
                            "choices": [
                                7449,
                                7448,
                                7447
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 56,
                            "question": "3954 + 3186",
                            "correctAnswer": 7140,
                            "choices": [
                                7139,
                                7140,
                                7141
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 57,
                            "question": "3126 + 1111",
                            "correctAnswer": 4237,
                            "choices": [
                                4238,
                                4237,
                                4236
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 58,
                            "question": "2875 + 4259",
                            "correctAnswer": 7134,
                            "choices": [
                                7133,
                                7135,
                                7134
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 59,
                            "question": "2740 + 1339",
                            "correctAnswer": 4079,
                            "choices": [
                                4079,
                                4078,
                                4080
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 60,
                            "question": "2048 + 1117",
                            "correctAnswer": 3165,
                            "choices": [
                                3165,
                                3164,
                                3166
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "subtraction",
            "difficulties": [
                {
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 61,
                            "question": "10 - 1",
                            "correctAnswer": 9,
                            "choices": [
                                10,
                                8,
                                9
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 62,
                            "question": "7 - 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 2,
                            "choices": [
                                3,
                                2,
                                1
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 63,
                            "question": "4 - 1",
                            "correctAnswer": 3,
                            "choices": [
                                2,
                                3,
                                4
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 64,
                            "question": "2 - 8",
                            "correctAnswer": -6,
                            "choices": [
                                -7,
                                -6,
                                -5
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 65,
                            "question": "6 - 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 1,
                            "choices": [
                                1,
                                2,
                                0
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 66,
                            "question": "3 - 9",
                            "correctAnswer": -6,
                            "choices": [
                                -5,
                                -6,
                                -7
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 67,
                            "question": "3 - 2",
                            "correctAnswer": 1,
                            "choices": [
                                0,
                                1,
                                2
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 68,
                            "question": "5 - 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 0,
                            "choices": [
                                1,
                                0,
                                -1
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 69,
                            "question": "10 - 10",
                            "correctAnswer": 0,
                            "choices": [
                                1,
                                -1,
                                0
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 70,
                            "question": "8 - 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 5,
                            "choices": [
                                5,
                                6,
                                4
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 71,
                            "question": "3 - 2",
                            "correctAnswer": 1,
                            "choices": [
                                1,
                                0,
                                2
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 72,
                            "question": "10 - 4",
                            "correctAnswer": 6,
                            "choices": [
                                5,
                                7,
                                6
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 73,
                            "question": "8 - 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 3,
                            "choices": [
                                3,
                                2,
                                4
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 74,
                            "question": "5 - 10",
                            "correctAnswer": -5,
                            "choices": [
                                -6,
                                -4,
                                -5
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 75,
                            "question": "7 - 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 4,
                            "choices": [
                                3,
                                4,
                                5
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 76,
                            "question": "8 - 4",
                            "correctAnswer": 4,
                            "choices": [
                                4,
                                5,
                                3
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 77,
                            "question": "6 - 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 3,
                            "choices": [
                                4,
                                3,
                                2
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 78,
                            "question": "2 - 4",
                            "correctAnswer": -2,
                            "choices": [
                                -2,
                                -3,
                                -1
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 79,
                            "question": "3 - 2",
                            "correctAnswer": 1,
                            "choices": [
                                2,
                                0,
                                1
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 80,
                            "question": "4 - 7",
                            "correctAnswer": -3,
                            "choices": [
                                -2,
                                -3,
                                -4
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 81,
                            "question": "22 - 64",
                            "correctAnswer": -42,
                            "choices": [
                                -42,
                                -41,
                                -43
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 82,
                            "question": "48 - 46",
                            "correctAnswer": 2,
                            "choices": [
                                3,
                                1,
                                2
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 83,
                            "question": "56 - 87",
                            "correctAnswer": -31,
                            "choices": [
                                -32,
                                -31,
                                -30
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 84,
                            "question": "77 - 78",
                            "correctAnswer": -1,
                            "choices": [
                                -1,
                                0,
                                -2
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 85,
                            "question": "84 - 52",
                            "correctAnswer": 32,
                            "choices": [
                                31,
                                32,
                                33
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 86,
                            "question": "31 - 56",
                            "correctAnswer": -25,
                            "choices": [
                                -26,
                                -25,
                                -24
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 87,
                            "question": "86 - 76",
                            "correctAnswer": 10,
                            "choices": [
                                9,
                                10,
                                11
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 88,
                            "question": "86 - 21",
                            "correctAnswer": 65,
                            "choices": [
                                64,
                                66,
                                65
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 89,
                            "question": "88 - 29",
                            "correctAnswer": 59,
                            "choices": [
                                59,
                                58,
                                60
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 90,
                            "question": "42 - 95",
                            "correctAnswer": -53,
                            "choices": [
                                -54,
                                -53,
                                -52
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 91,
                            "question": "89 - 89",
                            "correctAnswer": 0,
                            "choices": [
                                0,
                                1,
                                -1
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 92,
                            "question": "11 - 29",
                            "correctAnswer": -18,
                            "choices": [
                                -19,
                                -17,
                                -18
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 93,
                            "question": "61 - 34",
                            "correctAnswer": 27,
                            "choices": [
                                27,
                                28,
                                26
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 94,
                            "question": "25 - 39",
                            "correctAnswer": -14,
                            "choices": [
                                -13,
                                -14,
                                -15
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 95,
                            "question": "19 - 80",
                            "correctAnswer": -61,
                            "choices": [
                                -60,
                                -61,
                                -62
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 96,
                            "question": "87 - 57",
                            "correctAnswer": 30,
                            "choices": [
                                29,
                                31,
                                30
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 97,
                            "question": "88 - 96",
                            "correctAnswer": -8,
                            "choices": [
                                -9,
                                -8,
                                -7
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 98,
                            "question": "73 - 65",
                            "correctAnswer": 8,
                            "choices": [
                                9,
                                8,
                                7
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 99,
                            "question": "47 - 25",
                            "correctAnswer": 22,
                            "choices": [
                                22,
                                21,
                                23
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 100,
                            "question": "87 - 10",
                            "correctAnswer": 77,
                            "choices": [
                                77,
                                78,
                                76
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 101,
                            "question": "3761 - 4064",
                            "correctAnswer": -303,
                            "choices": [
                                -304,
                                -303,
                                -302
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 102,
                            "question": "1522 - 4508",
                            "correctAnswer": -2986,
                            "choices": [
                                -2985,
                                -2986,
                                -2987
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 103,
                            "question": "1333 - 1059",
                            "correctAnswer": 274,
                            "choices": [
                                275,
                                274,
                                273
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 104,
                            "question": "1841 - 3610",
                            "correctAnswer": -1769,
                            "choices": [
                                -1770,
                                -1768,
                                -1769
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 105,
                            "question": "4514 - 1007",
                            "correctAnswer": 3507,
                            "choices": [
                                3506,
                                3507,
                                3508
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 106,
                            "question": "2455 - 2226",
                            "correctAnswer": 229,
                            "choices": [
                                228,
                                229,
                                230
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 107,
                            "question": "2444 - 4515",
                            "correctAnswer": -2071,
                            "choices": [
                                -2070,
                                -2072,
                                -2071
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 108,
                            "question": "3994 - 2490",
                            "correctAnswer": 1504,
                            "choices": [
                                1505,
                                1504,
                                1503
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 109,
                            "question": "4747 - 4462",
                            "correctAnswer": 285,
                            "choices": [
                                286,
                                285,
                                284
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 110,
                            "question": "2086 - 1465",
                            "correctAnswer": 621,
                            "choices": [
                                620,
                                622,
                                621
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 111,
                            "question": "1182 - 2414",
                            "correctAnswer": -1232,
                            "choices": [
                                -1231,
                                -1232,
                                -1233
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 112,
                            "question": "3932 - 1626",
                            "correctAnswer": 2306,
                            "choices": [
                                2305,
                                2307,
                                2306
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 113,
                            "question": "3490 - 1638",
                            "correctAnswer": 1852,
                            "choices": [
                                1851,
                                1853,
                                1852
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 114,
                            "question": "1901 - 4053",
                            "correctAnswer": -2152,
                            "choices": [
                                -2151,
                                -2152,
                                -2153
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 115,
                            "question": "2450 - 3009",
                            "correctAnswer": -559,
                            "choices": [
                                -558,
                                -559,
                                -560
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 116,
                            "question": "3423 - 3110",
                            "correctAnswer": 313,
                            "choices": [
                                312,
                                313,
                                314
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 117,
                            "question": "4445 - 1009",
                            "correctAnswer": 3436,
                            "choices": [
                                3435,
                                3436,
                                3437
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 118,
                            "question": "3509 - 2791",
                            "correctAnswer": 718,
                            "choices": [
                                718,
                                717,
                                719
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 119,
                            "question": "1464 - 1837",
                            "correctAnswer": -373,
                            "choices": [
                                -372,
                                -373,
                                -374
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 120,
                            "question": "3619 - 1394",
                            "correctAnswer": 2225,
                            "choices": [
                                2224,
                                2226,
                                2225
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiplication",
            "difficulties": [
                {
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 121,
                            "question": "4 \u00d7 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 20,
                            "choices": [
                                21,
                                19,
                                20
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 122,
                            "question": "8 \u00d7 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 24,
                            "choices": [
                                24,
                                25,
                                23
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 123,
                            "question": "1 \u00d7 1",
                            "correctAnswer": 1,
                            "choices": [
                                0,
                                2,
                                1
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 124,
                            "question": "2 \u00d7 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 6,
                            "choices": [
                                5,
                                7,
                                6
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 125,
                            "question": "8 \u00d7 7",
                            "correctAnswer": 56,
                            "choices": [
                                55,
                                56,
                                57
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 126,
                            "question": "7 \u00d7 8",
                            "correctAnswer": 56,
                            "choices": [
                                56,
                                57,
                                55
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 127,
                            "question": "8 \u00d7 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 48,
                            "choices": [
                                49,
                                48,
                                47
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 128,
                            "question": "9 \u00d7 7",
                            "correctAnswer": 63,
                            "choices": [
                                64,
                                63,
                                62
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 129,
                            "question": "2 \u00d7 7",
                            "correctAnswer": 14,
                            "choices": [
                                14,
                                13,
                                15
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 130,
                            "question": "8 \u00d7 2",
                            "correctAnswer": 16,
                            "choices": [
                                15,
                                17,
                                16
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 131,
                            "question": "2 \u00d7 1",
                            "correctAnswer": 2,
                            "choices": [
                                2,
                                1,
                                3
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 132,
                            "question": "7 \u00d7 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 21,
                            "choices": [
                                21,
                                22,
                                20
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 133,
                            "question": "4 \u00d7 10",
                            "correctAnswer": 40,
                            "choices": [
                                41,
                                39,
                                40
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 134,
                            "question": "7 \u00d7 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 35,
                            "choices": [
                                36,
                                34,
                                35
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 135,
                            "question": "5 \u00d7 10",
                            "correctAnswer": 50,
                            "choices": [
                                51,
                                50,
                                49
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 136,
                            "question": "1 \u00d7 7",
                            "correctAnswer": 7,
                            "choices": [
                                7,
                                8,
                                6
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 137,
                            "question": "8 \u00d7 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 40,
                            "choices": [
                                39,
                                40,
                                41
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 138,
                            "question": "1 \u00d7 1",
                            "correctAnswer": 1,
                            "choices": [
                                2,
                                0,
                                1
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 139,
                            "question": "9 \u00d7 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 27,
                            "choices": [
                                26,
                                27,
                                28
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 140,
                            "question": "1 \u00d7 4",
                            "correctAnswer": 4,
                            "choices": [
                                5,
                                4,
                                3
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 141,
                            "question": "68 \u00d7 33",
                            "correctAnswer": 2244,
                            "choices": [
                                2244,
                                2243,
                                2245
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 142,
                            "question": "20 \u00d7 79",
                            "correctAnswer": 1580,
                            "choices": [
                                1580,
                                1581,
                                1579
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 143,
                            "question": "22 \u00d7 22",
                            "correctAnswer": 484,
                            "choices": [
                                483,
                                484,
                                485
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 144,
                            "question": "40 \u00d7 11",
                            "correctAnswer": 440,
                            "choices": [
                                440,
                                439,
                                441
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 145,
                            "question": "77 \u00d7 55",
                            "correctAnswer": 4235,
                            "choices": [
                                4236,
                                4234,
                                4235
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 146,
                            "question": "41 \u00d7 76",
                            "correctAnswer": 3116,
                            "choices": [
                                3115,
                                3116,
                                3117
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 147,
                            "question": "61 \u00d7 39",
                            "correctAnswer": 2379,
                            "choices": [
                                2380,
                                2379,
                                2378
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 148,
                            "question": "24 \u00d7 100",
                            "correctAnswer": 2400,
                            "choices": [
                                2401,
                                2399,
                                2400
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 149,
                            "question": "46 \u00d7 19",
                            "correctAnswer": 874,
                            "choices": [
                                873,
                                874,
                                875
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 150,
                            "question": "79 \u00d7 82",
                            "correctAnswer": 6478,
                            "choices": [
                                6479,
                                6478,
                                6477
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 151,
                            "question": "91 \u00d7 89",
                            "correctAnswer": 8099,
                            "choices": [
                                8099,
                                8098,
                                8100
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 152,
                            "question": "10 \u00d7 51",
                            "correctAnswer": 510,
                            "choices": [
                                511,
                                510,
                                509
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 153,
                            "question": "100 \u00d7 68",
                            "correctAnswer": 6800,
                            "choices": [
                                6801,
                                6799,
                                6800
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 154,
                            "question": "61 \u00d7 23",
                            "correctAnswer": 1403,
                            "choices": [
                                1402,
                                1403,
                                1404
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 155,
                            "question": "14 \u00d7 70",
                            "correctAnswer": 980,
                            "choices": [
                                980,
                                981,
                                979
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 156,
                            "question": "25 \u00d7 100",
                            "correctAnswer": 2500,
                            "choices": [
                                2499,
                                2501,
                                2500
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 157,
                            "question": "68 \u00d7 48",
                            "correctAnswer": 3264,
                            "choices": [
                                3264,
                                3263,
                                3265
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 158,
                            "question": "62 \u00d7 62",
                            "correctAnswer": 3844,
                            "choices": [
                                3843,
                                3844,
                                3845
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 159,
                            "question": "97 \u00d7 81",
                            "correctAnswer": 7857,
                            "choices": [
                                7856,
                                7858,
                                7857
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 160,
                            "question": "21 \u00d7 26",
                            "correctAnswer": 546,
                            "choices": [
                                545,
                                546,
                                547
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 161,
                            "question": "3508 \u00d7 2758",
                            "correctAnswer": 9675064,
                            "choices": [
                                9675065,
                                9675064,
                                9675063
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 162,
                            "question": "4801 \u00d7 1181",
                            "correctAnswer": 5669981,
                            "choices": [
                                5669981,
                                5669982,
                                5669980
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 163,
                            "question": "1685 \u00d7 1496",
                            "correctAnswer": 2520760,
                            "choices": [
                                2520760,
                                2520761,
                                2520759
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 164,
                            "question": "1603 \u00d7 3173",
                            "correctAnswer": 5086319,
                            "choices": [
                                5086318,
                                5086319,
                                5086320
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 165,
                            "question": "4855 \u00d7 2179",
                            "correctAnswer": 10579045,
                            "choices": [
                                10579046,
                                10579045,
                                10579044
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 166,
                            "question": "1969 \u00d7 1548",
                            "correctAnswer": 3048012,
                            "choices": [
                                3048013,
                                3048012,
                                3048011
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 167,
                            "question": "4921 \u00d7 4335",
                            "correctAnswer": 21332535,
                            "choices": [
                                21332536,
                                21332534,
                                21332535
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 168,
                            "question": "1935 \u00d7 1115",
                            "correctAnswer": 2157525,
                            "choices": [
                                2157524,
                                2157525,
                                2157526
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 169,
                            "question": "1232 \u00d7 4195",
                            "correctAnswer": 5168240,
                            "choices": [
                                5168239,
                                5168241,
                                5168240
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 170,
                            "question": "1912 \u00d7 4281",
                            "correctAnswer": 8185272,
                            "choices": [
                                8185271,
                                8185273,
                                8185272
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 171,
                            "question": "1693 \u00d7 2518",
                            "correctAnswer": 4262974,
                            "choices": [
                                4262973,
                                4262975,
                                4262974
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 172,
                            "question": "4025 \u00d7 4740",
                            "correctAnswer": 19078500,
                            "choices": [
                                19078499,
                                19078500,
                                19078501
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 173,
                            "question": "3293 \u00d7 3776",
                            "correctAnswer": 12434368,
                            "choices": [
                                12434368,
                                12434367,
                                12434369
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 174,
                            "question": "1882 \u00d7 4465",
                            "correctAnswer": 8403130,
                            "choices": [
                                8403129,
                                8403130,
                                8403131
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 175,
                            "question": "1367 \u00d7 3088",
                            "correctAnswer": 4221296,
                            "choices": [
                                4221295,
                                4221297,
                                4221296
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 176,
                            "question": "1476 \u00d7 1337",
                            "correctAnswer": 1973412,
                            "choices": [
                                1973413,
                                1973411,
                                1973412
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 177,
                            "question": "3162 \u00d7 3635",
                            "correctAnswer": 11493870,
                            "choices": [
                                11493869,
                                11493870,
                                11493871
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 178,
                            "question": "2418 \u00d7 2115",
                            "correctAnswer": 5114070,
                            "choices": [
                                5114069,
                                5114070,
                                5114071
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 179,
                            "question": "1762 \u00d7 3174",
                            "correctAnswer": 5592588,
                            "choices": [
                                5592588,
                                5592589,
                                5592587
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 180,
                            "question": "3953 \u00d7 4980",
                            "correctAnswer": 19685940,
                            "choices": [
                                19685940,
                                19685941,
                                19685939
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "division",
            "difficulties": [
                {
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 181,
                            "question": "40 \u00f7 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 8,
                            "choices": [
                                7,
                                8,
                                9
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 182,
                            "question": "6 \u00f7 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 2,
                            "choices": [
                                2,
                                3,
                                1
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 183,
                            "question": "24 \u00f7 8",
                            "correctAnswer": 3,
                            "choices": [
                                4,
                                3,
                                2
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 184,
                            "question": "48 \u00f7 8",
                            "correctAnswer": 6,
                            "choices": [
                                5,
                                7,
                                6
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 185,
                            "question": "40 \u00f7 10",
                            "correctAnswer": 4,
                            "choices": [
                                5,
                                3,
                                4
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 186,
                            "question": "7 \u00f7 1",
                            "correctAnswer": 7,
                            "choices": [
                                8,
                                7,
                                6
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 187,
                            "question": "12 \u00f7 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 4,
                            "choices": [
                                3,
                                4,
                                5
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 188,
                            "question": "30 \u00f7 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 6,
                            "choices": [
                                6,
                                7,
                                5
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 189,
                            "question": "20 \u00f7 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 4,
                            "choices": [
                                5,
                                3,
                                4
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 190,
                            "question": "5 \u00f7 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 1,
                            "choices": [
                                0,
                                2,
                                1
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 191,
                            "question": "10 \u00f7 1",
                            "correctAnswer": 10,
                            "choices": [
                                9,
                                10,
                                11
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 192,
                            "question": "32 \u00f7 8",
                            "correctAnswer": 4,
                            "choices": [
                                4,
                                3,
                                5
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 193,
                            "question": "48 \u00f7 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 8,
                            "choices": [
                                7,
                                9,
                                8
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 194,
                            "question": "12 \u00f7 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 2,
                            "choices": [
                                3,
                                2,
                                1
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 195,
                            "question": "6 \u00f7 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 1,
                            "choices": [
                                2,
                                0,
                                1
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 196,
                            "question": "18 \u00f7 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 3,
                            "choices": [
                                4,
                                2,
                                3
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 197,
                            "question": "21 \u00f7 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 7,
                            "choices": [
                                6,
                                8,
                                7
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 198,
                            "question": "63 \u00f7 9",
                            "correctAnswer": 7,
                            "choices": [
                                6,
                                7,
                                8
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 199,
                            "question": "80 \u00f7 10",
                            "correctAnswer": 8,
                            "choices": [
                                9,
                                7,
                                8
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 200,
                            "question": "6 \u00f7 1",
                            "correctAnswer": 6,
                            "choices": [
                                5,
                                7,
                                6
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 201,
                            "question": "80 \u00f7 10",
                            "correctAnswer": 8,
                            "choices": [
                                9,
                                8,
                                7
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 202,
                            "question": "120 \u00f7 8",
                            "correctAnswer": 15,
                            "choices": [
                                15,
                                16,
                                14
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 203,
                            "question": "98 \u00f7 14",
                            "correctAnswer": 7,
                            "choices": [
                                7,
                                8,
                                6
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 204,
                            "question": "63 \u00f7 9",
                            "correctAnswer": 7,
                            "choices": [
                                6,
                                7,
                                8
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 205,
                            "question": "16 \u00f7 4",
                            "correctAnswer": 4,
                            "choices": [
                                3,
                                5,
                                4
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 206,
                            "question": "156 \u00f7 13",
                            "correctAnswer": 12,
                            "choices": [
                                12,
                                11,
                                13
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 207,
                            "question": "168 \u00f7 14",
                            "correctAnswer": 12,
                            "choices": [
                                12,
                                13,
                                11
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 208,
                            "question": "70 \u00f7 14",
                            "correctAnswer": 5,
                            "choices": [
                                5,
                                4,
                                6
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 209,
                            "question": "361 \u00f7 19",
                            "correctAnswer": 19,
                            "choices": [
                                18,
                                20,
                                19
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 210,
                            "question": "270 \u00f7 15",
                            "correctAnswer": 18,
                            "choices": [
                                17,
                                19,
                                18
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 211,
                            "question": "136 \u00f7 17",
                            "correctAnswer": 8,
                            "choices": [
                                9,
                                8,
                                7
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 212,
                            "question": "380 \u00f7 19",
                            "correctAnswer": 20,
                            "choices": [
                                21,
                                19,
                                20
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 213,
                            "question": "96 \u00f7 8",
                            "correctAnswer": 12,
                            "choices": [
                                12,
                                11,
                                13
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 214,
                            "question": "380 \u00f7 19",
                            "correctAnswer": 20,
                            "choices": [
                                19,
                                21,
                                20
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 215,
                            "question": "225 \u00f7 15",
                            "correctAnswer": 15,
                            "choices": [
                                16,
                                15,
                                14
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 216,
                            "question": "32 \u00f7 16",
                            "correctAnswer": 2,
                            "choices": [
                                3,
                                1,
                                2
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 217,
                            "question": "91 \u00f7 13",
                            "correctAnswer": 7,
                            "choices": [
                                8,
                                6,
                                7
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 218,
                            "question": "117 \u00f7 13",
                            "correctAnswer": 9,
                            "choices": [
                                10,
                                9,
                                8
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 219,
                            "question": "39 \u00f7 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 13,
                            "choices": [
                                12,
                                13,
                                14
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 220,
                            "question": "45 \u00f7 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 15,
                            "choices": [
                                16,
                                15,
                                14
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "problems": [
                        {
                            "id": 221,
                            "question": "34 \u00f7 2",
                            "correctAnswer": 17,
                            "choices": [
                                17,
                                18,
                                16
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 222,
                            "question": "360 \u00f7 20",
                            "correctAnswer": 18,
                            "choices": [
                                19,
                                18,
                                17
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 223,
                            "question": "28 \u00f7 7",
                            "correctAnswer": 4,
                            "choices": [
                                3,
                                5,
                                4
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 224,
                            "question": "78 \u00f7 6",
                            "correctAnswer": 13,
                            "choices": [
                                13,
                                14,
                                12
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 225,
                            "question": "360 \u00f7 18",
                            "correctAnswer": 20,
                            "choices": [
                                20,
                                21,
                                19
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 226,
                            "question": "51 \u00f7 3",
                            "correctAnswer": 17,
                            "choices": [
                                18,
                                16,
                                17
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 227,
                            "question": "120 \u00f7 8",
                            "correctAnswer": 15,
                            "choices": [
                                15,
                                16,
                                14
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 228,
                            "question": "72 \u00f7 8",
                            "correctAnswer": 9,
                            "choices": [
                                10,
                                9,
                                8
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 229,
                            "question": "54 \u00f7 9",
                            "correctAnswer": 6,
                            "choices": [
                                7,
                                5,
                                6
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 230,
                            "question": "224 \u00f7 14",
                            "correctAnswer": 16,
                            "choices": [
                                17,
                                16,
                                15
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 231,
                            "question": "190 \u00f7 10",
                            "correctAnswer": 19,
                            "choices": [
                                20,
                                19,
                                18
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 232,
                            "question": "162 \u00f7 18",
                            "correctAnswer": 9,
                            "choices": [
                                9,
                                10,
                                8
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 233,
                            "question": "105 \u00f7 7",
                            "correctAnswer": 15,
                            "choices": [
                                14,
                                15,
                                16
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 234,
                            "question": "198 \u00f7 11",
                            "correctAnswer": 18,
                            "choices": [
                                18,
                                19,
                                17
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 235,
                            "question": "95 \u00f7 5",
                            "correctAnswer": 19,
                            "choices": [
                                18,
                                20,
                                19
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 236,
                            "question": "288 \u00f7 16",
                            "correctAnswer": 18,
                            "choices": [
                                17,
                                18,
                                19
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 237,
                            "question": "154 \u00f7 14",
                            "correctAnswer": 11,
                            "choices": [
                                11,
                                10,
                                12
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 238,
                            "question": "90 \u00f7 15",
                            "correctAnswer": 6,
                            "choices": [
                                5,
                                7,
                                6
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 239,
                            "question": "210 \u00f7 15",
                            "correctAnswer": 14,
                            "choices": [
                                14,
                                15,
                                13
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 240,
                            "question": "112 \u00f7 14",
                            "correctAnswer": 8,
                            "choices": [
                                8,
                                9,
                                7
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}